こんにちは。カナダでエンジニアをやっているガックンです。今、
エンジニアやIT関係者が実際の仕事で英語をとっさに話す練習が
できるDevEnglishGymというアプリを開発しています
。
Are you still on track to finish the notification
settings today?
I was supposed to finish the notification settings
yesterday.
However, old-user migration took longer than
expected.
The implementation has been done, but there are two
tests failing.
I don't think it's going to affect the overall
release.
僕の回答がここに出ています
今回の達成度3分の2ですね
ただし新しい完了見込みである
今日の午後3時までが入っていないため相手が次の予定を判断でき
ません
というふうにフィードバックされています
では、改善点を意識して再回答していきたいと思います。
I'm actually a little bit behind schedule.
Legacy-user migration took longer than expected.
The implementation is done.
However, there are two tests failing at the moment.
I expect to finish by 3 p.m. today.
I don't think it's going to affect the release date.
さっき初回は3分の2だったんですけど
今回再回答で3分の3
3分の3の達成度となりました